John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - Dept. L: Environment Legislative Files, 1/1/1991-12/31/1991 (Box 78)
    S. 1862 - Wildlife Refuge Mgmt. Act; Space Station; S. 58--The National Biological Diversity Act of 1991; Lewis & Clark Center - Explore; Lorton Landfill Amendment 101st Congress, 1991 DC Appropriations; Metro D. C. Waste Management Study Robb; 1991 Clean Coal Projects; RCRA's "Derived From" Rule: A Regulation Frustrating RCRA's Goals of Resource Conservation and Recovery
  - Dept. L: Materials related to the International Space Station, 1/1/1992-12/31/1996 (Box 79)
    Background on Space Station: Coalition Information; Background on Space Station: Congressional Quarterly Articles; Background on Space Station: Memos; Space Station [binder]; Background on Space Station: Space Station Debate 8/2/1994 VA - HUD Appropriations; Background on Space Station: Articles on Space Station; Background on Space Station: "Dear Colleague" Letters; Background on Space Station: 1. Draft Statement on Space Station 2. "Benefits to Humanity" Congressional Research Service Memo [binder]; Space Station Articles 1995; Space Station Freedom, Reston, VA. Facility; Background on Space Station [presentation folder] Space Station Articles; The Superconducting Super Collider [binder]; Background on Space Station: C. R. S. Reports; Senator Warner Space Station Statement Sept. 26/1995; Space Station Debate 1995 Background Information
  - Dept. L: Base Closure and Realignment Commission (BRAC 91 BRAC 93), 1/1/1991-12/31/1993 (Box 80)
    NADEP Norfolk [presentation folder]; untitled: Itinerary for 6/10/1993 [binder]; Norfolk - Miscellaneous SC [presentation folder]; Naval Undersea Warfare Center NUWC [presentation folder]; NADEP Norfolk [VHS]; Base Closure 1991 [presentation folder]; Naval Surface Warfare Center - Dahlgren [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: Republican Task Force for Defense Build-Down (BRAC 1992), 1/1/1991-12/31/1992 (Box 81)
    Senate Republican Tf. for Defense Conversion April - June 1992 [binder]; Economic Impact of the Military Draw Down on Virginia, Book 4 (References) [binder]; Economic Impact of the Military Draw Down on Virginia, Book 3 (References) [binder]
  - Dept. L: Files from Remmel Dickinson from the 100th Congress, 1/1/1991-12/31/1993 (Box 82)
    Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: Committee Testimony; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: General Information; Federal Employees EEDC; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: Position Articles and Letters; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: Letters - Oppose; Hatch Act 1993; PERRY POST OFFICE; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress.: Letters - Pro; Early Retirement Bill; Hatch Act 1991; S 349 - Lobbying Disclosure Act; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: Newspaper Articles; S.1 - Unfunded Mandate; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: Reports and Research; Hatch Act; Nat. and Comn. Service - 1991-; H.R. 782; Hatch Act (HR3400) 100th Congress: Bulletins and Newsletters
  - Dept. L: Lori Nirenberg, taxes, 1/1/1991-12/31/1994 (Box 83)
    Front Royal VA Customs Staffing Reduction; State Unclaimed Property Equitable escheatment; FASB S1175; Fannie May and State Information on Branching; Freddie Mac; Federal Reserve System; VAT; CDBG; Bank Regulation; National Customs Automation System; Capital Gains (2?); IRAS; Derivatives; 1992 End of Session Notes on Banking Legislation; FIRRea Report; Defense Production Act; Credit Crunch; Credit Union Information; BANK Regulator Consolidation; Banking Overview; H.R. 11 Tax Bill 10/1992 [presentation folder]; State Taxes; Secondary Mortgage Market; 1991 Virginia Tax Exempt Bonds; Taxation of Corporate Sponsorship; Targeted Jobs Tax Credit; IRS: Corporate Gifts to Charities Abroad; 1992 Tax Guide; 1994 Banking Bills; Mr. Gates; Excise Taxes & Retrogresivity; Richmond Redcup and Housing Authority; Passive Losses; Shelby/Mack ECO Growth Act; Larry Lindsey Federal Reserve Nomination; A History of the Thrift Industry and Thrift Information; Luxury Tax; Mortgage Revenue Bonds
  - Dept. L: Environment, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990 (Box 84)
    EPA: RCRA Reforms; 101st Congress, 2nd Session, EPW Hearing on Interstate Solid Waste Transport, 7/18/1990; RCRA Amendments [presentation folder]: Lautenberg Amendments, Durenberger Amendment, Symms Amendment, Jeffords Amendments, Moynihan Amendments., Woffard Amendments, Smith Amendment, Metzenbaum Amendment, Graham Amendment, Reid-Warner-Scrap Amendment; Recycling Hearing: Responsible Entity, 3/5/92; 102nd Congress EPW Hearing, Interstate Transportation of Solid Waste, 6/18/1991; Recycling Hearing 3/5/92; S 976; RCRA: Industrial D; Untitled presentation folder: Correspondence
  - Dept. L: Tax Agriculture Files, 1/1/1986-12/31/1990 (Box 85)
    RTC-Clippings, etc.; KIT WEBB (IRS Case); NAFTA; Dislocated Workers - Job Assistance; MPVs; Entitlements; Social Security Notch; Caribbean Basin Trade; Flood Insurance-Research; SSDI Reform; World Bank; Tax Extenders; Pension Plans-Cross Testing; European Bank for Reconstruction and Development (EBRD); S. 1633 [envelope]; Untitled Folder: Clippings; GATT; EKG, Young Physician etc.; H.C. Meetings with Constituents (notes); S.265-Economic Growth and Regulatory; 3/1992 Tax Bill - Rejected; Trade; AMT (Alternative Minimum Tax); FDIC-Bank Regulations Capital to Asset Ratios; Truth in Tax-Exempt Giving Act; Medicare-Medicaid (CRS, etc.); Gas Tax BTU & Transportation Tax; Senator Warner-NAFTA; Trade: Burlington Ind.; D.C. Taxicab; Community Development Banking Act; General Banking; Mortgage Revenue Bonds; Otolaryngologists/Plastic Surgeons; Credit Unions; Home Health Care; Homelessness; Medicare Physician Payment Reform; Diversification of Financial Services; Social Security; Cola; Vat Tax; Estate Tax; IRS Code-Section 936
  - Dept. L: BRAC, 1/1/1994-12/31/1994 (Box 86)
    An Analysis of the Industrial Structure of Virginia's Defense Industry, 2/1993; Loose Papers: Clippings, Memos, Charts, Faxes; Gov's Commission on Def Conversion & Econ. Adjustment; Defense Conversion; Governor's Conference on Defense Conversion [2 portfolio folders]; A Profile of Defense Procurement Spending in Virginia Defense Expenditures in Virginia, 7/1992; Governor's Commission on Defense Conversion and Economic Adjustment [binder]; Untitled Folder: Talking Points and Clippings; Special Edition; Governor's Commission on Defense Conversion and Economic Adjustment, First Report to the Governor, 11/1992; Defense Cuts: State and Local Action for Economic Adjustment; Norfolk-Defense Conversion; Estimated Private Sector Defense Employment by Industry and Region in Virginia, 2/1993; Listing Virginia's Prime Defense Contractors Ranked by Contract, 2/1993; A CBO Study: The Economic Effects of Reduced Defense Spending, 2/1992; Crystal City Defense Conversion; Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation [United States Senate portfolio folder]
  - Dept. L: Civil Rights Legislative Files, 1/1/1991-12/31/1993 (Box 87)
    Hatch Act [binder]; N View; Hydrosystems; Virginia Governor Report on International Trade Development (2/5/1993); Turbines and Generations; Merck Foreign Trade Zone; Active Matrix Liquid Crystal; Andrews & Assc., Chocolate Manufacturers; Untitled Folder: Correspondence, Clippings, Portfolio Folder; US Chili/FTA; BTG; Lori: Civil Rights 1991 [presentation folder]: Memorandum, Clippings, Reports, Press Releases, Letter and Backup Binder; Civil Rights Legislation 1990 [presentation folder]: Correspondence, Memorandum, Reports
  - Dept. L: Environment Projects, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990 (Box 88)
    Solid Waste in General; 102nd Congress - 1st Session Subcommittee on Environ. Prot. BASEL CONVENTION (7/26/91); Basel Convention-International Tran boundary Movement of Hazardous Waste--Memorandum of Law; Points of Contact; Recycling Legislation Senator Warner; RCRA: Hazard Waste Incinerators; RCRA: Shell Oil vs. EPA; 102nd Congress Legislation Resource Conservation and Recovery Act--Solid Waste; RCRA: Hazardous Wastes; S. 1429 Hazardous Waste Reduction; Correspondence
  - Dept. L: Federal Judges, 1/1/1991-12/31/1992 (Box 89)
    Brinkema, Leoni Judge-Eastern; Eastern, Smith, Rebecca B.; Farrell, Thomas Judge-Eastern; Blank, Irving Easter Judgeship; Wright, Wiley Judgeship-Eastern; Herman, Sharon Judge-Eastern; Judge Williams Vacancy; Morgan, Henry Judge-Eastern; Lawson, Thomas Judge-Eastern; Berkley, Waverly Judgeship - Eastern; U.S. Marshal - Eastern District; Sheridan, Paul Judge-Eastern; Eastern District Judgeship 1991; Jackson, Raymond Judgeship-East; Jackson, Raymond Judge-Eastern; Judgeships - Eastern District; Cynkar, Robert Judge-Eastern; Anderson, Alvin Judgeship - Eastern; King, Ray Judge-Eastern; Humphreys, Robert Judge-Eastern; Clark, Mort Judgeship-Eastern; Slater, Mildred Judge-Eastern; Townsend, Lee Judge-Eastern; Ellis, T. S. Judge-Eastern Dist.; Eastern - Townsend, H. Lee; Eastern District Judgeships; Glaser, Richard Judge-Eastern; Payne, Robber Judgeship-Eastern; Lemons, Donald Judgeship-Eastern; David, Buddy Judge-Eastern; Bishop, Bruce Judge-Eastern; Mahoney, Maureen Judge-Eastern; Murphy, Gregory Judgeship-East; U.S. Judgeships; Western - Wilson, same
  - Dept. L: BRAC, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 90)
    Economic Impact of the Military Draw Down on Virginia, Book 1 [binder]; Economic Impact of the Military Draw Down on Virginia, Book 2 [binder]
  - Dept. L: Small Business, Kerry Small Business Bill, White House Conference, A-E Files (Box 91)
    5 folders, A-E containing correspondence, reports, notes; Regulatory Flexibility Act [presentation folder]; GAO Report: Agencies Compliance [presentation folder]; Hearing 3/8/1995 [presentation folder]; White House Small Business Conference; Articles, General Information on Reg Flex [presentation folder]; Kerry Small Business Bill 1994; SBA Chief Advocate Info [presentation folder]; Regulatory Flexibility Bill [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L- BRAC, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993 (Box 92)
    6/11/1993 Hearings; Final Closure- Articles; Norfolk Shipyard; NESEC Portsmouth; The Honorable John W. Warner, United States Senate, Russell Senate Office Bldg. [binder]
  - Dept. L: BRAC, correspondence, reports, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990 (Box 93)
    Letters- BRAC 93; Navy Correspondence; BRAC- Letters; VA Hearing- 4/20/1993; Base Closure Data [envelope]; GAO Reports, Process; Vint Hill Farm Station; Crystal City- Miscellaneous- Post BRAC; Crystal City- Court Challenge; Crystal City-Purchase Option; BRAC Transition Initiative; BRAC- Report to President; BRAC- Public Law 101-510; NADED- Conversion; Military Cleanup; Personal Notes
  - Dept. L- BRAC Commission, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993 (Box 94)
    Richmond- DOD Data Center, Other Virginia Closings/Issues; Fort Lee; Loose paper: Report of Secretary of Navy, Defense Base Closure and Realignment Act of 1990; Fort Monroe; NAS Oceana
  - Dept. L- Justice Legislative Files, 1/1/1991-3/31/1993 (Box 95)
    Institute of Packaging Professionals; Charity Bill; Equal Remedies Act (Civil Rights); European Trade; NAFTA; Housing Issues (gen); NAOMI: RTC; Clarence Thomas; Loose Paper: Housing Affairs
  - Dept. L: Energy, Veterans Affairs, Legislative Files, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993 (Box 96)
    1993 EPW, April-June; 1993 EPW, July-September; 1993 Rules; 1993 EPW, October-December; 1993 EPW January-March; 1993 Energy, July-December; 1993 Energy, January-June; 1993 Governmental Affairs; 1993 For Relations; 1993 Labor; 1993 Judiciary
  - Dept. L: BRAC, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 97)
    Base Transition Offices; Arlington/Crystal City
  - Dept. L: George Washington Forest, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993 (Box 98)
    Record of Decision, FINAL Environmental Impact Statement for the Revised Land and Resource Management Plan; George Washington National Forest Maps [shrink wrapped package]; Final Environmental Impact Statement-George Washington National Forest; Comments and Responses: Appendix I to the FINAL Environmental Impact Statement-George Washington National Forest; A Summary of the FINAL Environmental Impact Statement for the Revised Land and Resource Management Plan
  - Dept. L: Energy-Veterans Affairs, Legislative Files, 1/1/1991-10/15/1994 (Box 99)
    Legislative Activities (1/5/1993-7/10/1993); Legislative Activities (1/3/1991-7/18/1992); 1993 Veterans; Legislative Activities (1/5/1993-10/15/1994); 1993 Finance; Legislative Activities (1/5/1991-4/25/1992); Old Misc.; Legislative Activities (1/3/1991-1/11/1992); 1993 SBA
  - Dept. L- Legislative Activities Books, 1/15/1979-1/4/1997 (Box 100)
    14 Legislative Activities Books: The Honorable John W. Warner of Virginia
  - Dept. L- NAFTA Trade Legislative Files, 1/1/1989-12/31/1993 (Box 101)
    Virginia Port of Entry; NAFTA (publications and correspondence )
  - Dept. L- NAFTA- Trade Legislative Files, 1/1/1991-12/31/1992 (Box 102)
    Virginia Dept of World Trade; Dunkel Draft (GATT); Rosemary O'Brian Saferco; Elastic Corporation; Germany Trip; China Slave Labor; Textiles; Mr. Fagan: EEC; Enterprise for the Americas; Va Port Authority (fumigant on logs); Japan's Securities Crisis; EC Oil Seed Subsidy; NATO; Dept of Labor trade Adjustment; Multi-Purpose Vehicles; Free Trade Makes Sense; Rules of Origin; Japanese Construction; Hormone- Free Trade; Hercules/Aqualon; Furniture Manufacturers
  - Dept. L- WAR Powers Act, 1/1/1973-12/31/1987 (Box 103)
    Loose Paper: copies of bill amendments, rough drafts; Military Retirement; Alternative Persian Gulf War Powers; Nomination Issues; Loose paper: photocopies of congressional record, speeches and reports; Untitled Folder: copies of amendments; Untitled Folder: National Security issues; Loose paper: books dealing with the interpretation of the War Powers Act, and copies of amendments
  - Dept. L: Files and correspondence related to clean air legislation and environmental issues, 1/1/1987-12/31/1990 (Box 104)
    COE - 25,000 Ton Policy; Lawson Jones - COE - Wetlands; New File: EPW, EP Sub, Clean Air, Municipal Waste Incinerators [presentation folder]; EPW 101, EP Subcommittee, Clean Air, Acid Rain [presentation folder]; New File: EPW 101, EP Sub, Clean Air, State Mtgs.; 1987-1988 Appropriations; New File: EPW 101, EP Sub, Clean Air, ADMINISTRATION DOCS [presentation folder]; EPW 101, EP Sub, Clean Air, Nonattainment [presentation folder]; EPW 101, EP Sub, Clean Air, Warner Rocket Amendment [presentation folder]; 1990 Clean Air Act Warner Acid Rain Amendment; Corps of Engineers - Dinwiddie; EPW 101, EP Sub, Clean Air, 1990 Acr: Bills, Reports [folder & packet]; Poquoson River; TOXICS [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: Copies of bills co-sponsored by Sen. Warner and related correspondence, 1/1/1989-12/31/1990 (Box 105)
    Co-Sponsored 1989 [presentation folder]; No Position 1990 July - Dec [empty presentation folder]; No Position [empty presentation folder]; Co- Sponsored 1990 [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: EPW Committee- Public Works Hearings, 1/1/1989-12/31/1995 (Box 106)
    EPW Subcommittee on Water Resources, Transportation and Infrastructure Hearing on Public Buildings-GSA, 3/20/1990; EPW Mark-up, FWI Committee Meeting 9/5/1990; Subcommittee on Water Resources Transportation and Infrastructure Hearing on Infrastructure Council Act, 7/17/1990; Economic Development Administration Budget FY 1991; S. 2740 Water resources Development Act 1990 Sections 311 and 312; Economic Development Administration 1989 Annual Report; Department of Transportation FY 1991 Budget; EPW Press Conference, Rebuilding the Foundations: State and Local Public Works Financing and Management; EPW Subcommittee on Water Resources, Transportation and Infrastructure Hearing, 4/19/1990 S. 2183; EPW Reconciliation FY 1991-1995; Water Resources Bill Letter from Congressman Bennett, Nassau County, Florida; Water Resources Development Act 1990-Conference; Untitled folder: Testimonies and reference materials; 1990 Water Resources Act EPW Hearing Mark-up 5/22/1990; Appropriations - Transportation, Manassas Airport [presentation folder]; National Highway Fatality and Injury Reduction Act (Helmets and Seatbelts) 1989; Subcommittee on Water Resources, Transportation, and Infrastructure 3/1st Hearing (1990 WRDA); HR 5314 Water Resources Development Act, Amendment by Cong. Sisisky; Untitled folder containing speeches and correspondence; Statement by Senator John Warner, EPW Mark-up Water Resources Dev. Act S. 2183; Appalachian Regional Commission 1991 Budget Issues; EPW Subcommittee on Water Resources, Transportation, and Infrastructure Hearing ARC and EDA 9/13/1990 [presentation folder]; National Highway Fatality and Injury Reduction Act (Helmets and Seatbelts) 1989; Water Resources Development Act 1990, Congresswoman Lynn Martin Letter; Environment and Public Works, Mark-up Public Buildings, 6/12/1990; Federal Aviation Administration City of Manassas Airport; U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Fiscal Year 1991; EPW Federal Infrastructure Council Act (Burdick) [presentation folder]; EPW 5/15/1990 Hearing on Assistance for developing Environmental Facilities; EPW Polling, 4 Water Resources Resolutions
  - Dept. L: Legislative Files, 101st Congress, 1/1/1990-12/31/1991 (Box 107)
    Gulf Pollution Task Force Advisory Meeting III, Briefing Notebook, 7/11/1991; EPW: General: Environmental Strategy/Legislation; NEA Funding 101st Congress, Warner's Bill S. 3010; 101st Legis/ Sponsored and Co-Sponsored [4 envelopes]; Ethyl Additive; NPS Huntley Meadows Lockheed Blvd.; Ivan Selin/Mike Hayden Nomination 5/21/1991
  - Dept. L: Energy Projects, 1/1/1984-12/31/1991 (Box 108)
    SBIR Hearing-House 11/26/1991; Enhanced Modular Signal Processor (UYS-2); Camp Picket/A. P. Hill Realignment; Congressional Monitor; Assault Weapons; Closed Cases; Closed Cases; Canadair Challenger Briefing [binder]; 10/29/1991 Hearing/SB and Kuwait; Base Closure- Credit Union; Navy Consolidation GSA; Miscellaneous; VA Forum Speech 11/14/1991; Loose Correspondence regarding General Dynamics; Army Corps Reorganization; GSA/Navy Building Procurement; CIA Relocation; Navy Consolidations
  - Dept. L: REM Legislative Files, 1/1/1984-12/31/1986 (Box 109)
    American Psychological Association; Job Corps; US Post Office Congressional Briefing Material, 99th Congress (2 copies) [loose]; American Amputee Foundation; Southern Regional Task Force on Infant Mortality Interim Report and A Fiscal Imperative [loose]; National Association of College Admissions Counselors; Committee on Aging Testimonies [untitled]; American Diabetes Association; Background on the Civil Service Retirement System [loose]; Vocational Education; A Report to Congress from the Office of Special Counsel [loose]; American Lung Association of Virginia; Reports on Aging, GRH and Elderly [envelope]; Loose correspondence, tax forms, newsletters; American Postal Workers Union; Juvenile Diabetes Foundation International; Report to the Chairman Special Committee on Aging United States Senate: Medicare's Policies and Prospective Payment Rates [loose]; Pension Forum IV: Federal Pension Speech [envelope]; Loose documents regarding Medicare and retirement; Age Discrimination in Employment Act; Clippings and reports regarding Social Security [envelope]; Testimonies regarding pacemakers [loose]; American Library Association, Education Reform; United Cerebral Palsy Association Congressional Visits Information Packet; Annual Report of the Board of Trustees of the Federal Old-Age and Survivors Insurance and Disability Insurance Trust Funds [loose]
  - Dept. L: Military Notebooks, Law, reference materials, 1/1/1973-12/31/1991 (Box 110)
    US Army Senior Officer Legal Orientation Course Desk Book, 1991 [binder]; Military Law Reporter, Volume 19 (1991) [binder]; Fiscal Law Desk Book, 32nd Fiscal Law Course, 1991 [binder]; Military Law Reporter, Volume 1 (1973) [binder]
  - Dept. L: Agriculture-Energy Legislative Files, 1/1/1994-12/31/1995 (Box 111)
    1995 Education; 1995 Budget; 1995 Press Releases; 1995 Agriculture; 1995 Banking; 1995 Administration; 1995 Energy; 1994 Speeches/Floor Statements; 1995 Aging; 1995 Commerce; 1995 Speeches/Floor Statements, January - June; 1995 Armed Services; 1995 Appropriations; 1995 Speeches-Floor Statements, July - December
  - Dept. L: Environment and Public Works Committee hearings May - July 1989, arranged by meeting topic and date, 5/10/1989-7/24/1989 (Box 112)
    EPW Committee Hearing 101 Congress CFC Hearing, 5/19/89; EPW Committee 101 Congress Subcommittee Hearing -- OIL SPILLS 7/13/1989; EPW Committee Hearing 101 Congress Toxic Chemical Use in Aerospace, 7/5/89; EPW Committee - 101st Congress Oil Spill Legislation Hearing, 7/21/89 [empty folder]; EPW Committee Hearing 101 Congress Right to Know Pollution Data, 5/10/89; EPW Committee Hearing 101 Congress North American Wetlands Conservation Act, 6/1/89; EPW - 101st Congress Hearing on Oil Spill Legislation (7/21/89) [empty folder]; EPW - 101st Congress RCRA Authorization; EPW Committee Hearing 101 Congress Clean Water Oversight, 6/16/89; EPW - 101st Congress Turner Conference Hearing (7/24/89); EPW Committee Mark-Up 101 Congress S.804, North American Wetlands, 6/22/89; EPW Committee - 101st Congress Oil Spill Legislation Hearing, 7/21/89; EPW 101 Congress Hearing Re: NRC Reorganization, 7/19/89; EPW Committee 101 Congress Full Committee Reconciliation Mark-Up, 7/20/89; EPW Committee 101 Congress Subcommittee Hearing Coastal Pollution, 7/12 & 7/25/89; EPW - 101st Congress Full Committee Business Meeting, T 7/20/89 [empty folder]; EPW Committee101 Congress Full Committee Mark-Up S.804 North American Wetlands, 7/20/89
  - Dept. L: 102nd and 103rd Congresses, Co-signed and Co-sponsored Letters, 1/1/1991-12/31/1994 (Box 113)
    1993 Speeches/Floor Statements; 103rd Congress Co-signed 1994; 102nd Congress Co-signed 1991; 102nd Congress Co-sponsored 1992; 102nd Congress Co-signed 1992; 102nd Congress Co-sponsored 1991; 103rd Congress Sponsored Leg.; 103rd Congress Co-signed 1993; 103rd Congress Co-sponsored 1993; 103rd Congress Co-sponsored 1994; 103rd Congress No Positions 1994; 103rd Congress Dear Colleagues; 102nd Congress Sponsored Leg.
  - Dept. L: Remmel Dickinson, 1/1/1984-12/31/1986 (Box 114)
    OPM RIF Regulations; Merit Cash Awards; untitled: FBI contract [envelope]; Revenue Forgone / Blind Mailings; Reduction - In - Force; Pay Comparability Raise; ICC Pay Appropriations; NASA Engineers; Federal Government Service Task Force [envelope]; Pay Raise; Postmaster; United States Office of Personnel Management News [packet]; Merit Pay, Pay Equity / H.R. 5680 S958; Public Employee Appreciation Day; Lorton Retirees; loose papers: civil service retirement; Merit Pay; New Federal Retirement; DoD Civilian Moving Expenses; Prince William Postal; Moving Expenses Amendments - 1985; 1989 - Relocation / Last Move Home; retirement benefits [packet]; Government Reorganization - OMB Plan; Recommendations
  - Dept. L: Sen. Warner Voting Record for the 99th-101st Congresses, and legislative files, arranged together by subject, 1/1/1984-12/31/1990 (Box 115)
    Warner Record: Finance / Taxes; Warner Record: TRADE; Warner Record: Social Security (Senior Citizens); Warner Record: Banking / Housing / Urban Affairs; Warner Record: Judiciary; Warner Record: Budget & Appropriations; Warner Record: Environment; Warner Record: Education; Warner Record: Regulatory Reform; Warner Record: Commerce / Small Business; Warner Record: Savings & Loans; Warner Record: Energy / Natural Resources; Warner Record: Labor; Warner Record: National Security; Warner Record: Transportation; Warner Record: Health; Warner Record: Welfare; Warner Record: Aging; Warner Record: Federal Employees
  - Dept. L.: Susan Magill - energy, military, 1/1/1987-12/31/1991 (Box 116)